Thank you.
>> Uh it's special. Um I've dreamed of this
my whole life. Uh I know my Malita are
proud. Um yeah, this is a dream come
true.
>> As you know, there were a lot of
cheering for you. Anything you want to
say to all the Mexican fans right now
cheering you?
>> Thank you. It means a lot. Um I'm filled
with love. My family's filled with love
for all the support. Uh and I just love
being able just to be me to the fullest.
Thank you.
Yeah.
>> Yeah. It's combined effort, you know, to
be able to do kind of run the scheme
that we do and have success the way we
have. It it just takes talent, you know,
it starts up front. Uh Byron Murphy,
honestly, is kind of the the heartbeat
of our defense. Um and he's just unsung
hero. I think his name needs to be
mentioned more. um him, Leonard
Williams, Jiren Reed up front, the depth
that we have in the interior and then
our edges our killers. Um, you see Boya,
you see, uh, D Hall, you see D Law. Um,
they just they make plays and so it
starts up front. And the linebackers,
Ernest is, you know, as our leader, our
captain. Um, him and Drake have been
playing good ball. And then I would say
our rookie, man. Um, having our rookie
young Demon War. Uh, him and, uh, him
and Spoon, man, playing that that slot
role. They're they're killers. They're
some of the best players in this league.
And so allowing that to happen when they
can be stout versus the run. um having
our fort down be stop versus run. It
allows me to be free. Allows me and Kobe
our corners to be free uh and just play
ball. So it's talent. It's
>> Yeah, exactly. So when we do pressure,
then we're able to get home because he's
already panicked and so yeah, we had a
good plan. Shout out to Mike McDonald.
Um a lot of lot of thought, a lot of
effort, a lot of adjustments the whole
week. We installed some stuff yesterday.
Uh it always goes up into the whistle
because we're just always chasing that
edge.
you guys to be loose and focused.
Loose and focus. What would you describe
if you could take two other
>> Oh, two other words. No. Well, I'll talk
about loose and focus. Like when you see
us, if you, you know, have eyes on us in
the locker room uh at halftime on the
sideline, we're just we love each other.
Like we we are constantly messing
around. We're not too serious. We don't
take ourselves too serious, but when
that that whistle sounds, when we step
across those white lines, then it's
focused. That's kind of the message of
it. It's like we allowed to have fun.
Mike allows us to have fun. Coaching
staff, everybody is always laughing and
having a good time. But then when
there's work to be done, we we go to
work.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. K9 is special. Uh there's not a
person in the building that doesn't
believe that, you know, we're a better
team when when he's going. And so, um,
to see him and when he gets Super Bowl
MVP is crazy. He's earned it. I mean,
there's been so much doubt on his name.
He shows up each day. He's a quiet guy,
but he's a menace with that ball in his
hands. And so, he showed it today
winning the MVP is crazy. This whole
playoff run, obviously, Zack, we love
him. Uh, and it was vital having them
both of them all season. Um, but it was
more on K9's shoulders when Zach went
down. Um, and so he showed up for us in
a big way. Talk talk about your
interception. Dream come true.
>> Yeah.
>> Dream come true. Of course it is. Uh you
know I'd be kidding you if I didn't
dream of that in the backyard when I was
you know 8 10 8 nine years old. Um to
see that ball in the air. You know it
was right to me. Uh only thought in my
mind is just catch it. your the
game on the secondary.
>> Yeah, that's been our theme all game.
Like we have killers across the board.
Everybody uh holds their own weight and
and has that tip on their shoulder to be
successful. Um but allow our front being
able to, you know, take on double teams.
Um play with four down, play in sub
packages, uh as strong and as stout as
we do, it frees us up. So we can just
make plays and just roam on secondary.
Uh you see our secondary all year making
plays like that. Uh and I'm lucky to
have made one today.
>> Yeah,
>> it's pretty cool. I'm biased, but I love
that we had the performance today uh on
the on the big stage because it's been
the work, man. Like from training camp
on, there's been such a high standard
for how we conduct ourselves. Um and
it's coming fruition today. And then the
story of the game today was just
controlling the ball. We wanted to win
the turnover battle. Uh and we did in a
big way. What was it? 3 0. Um and so it
was a team effort. You know, the offense
they drove the ball on the field. You
know, we scored when we needed to. And
Jai kicking field goals the way he's
always done all season. Uh record
holder. Um and defense, we just we love
uh just playing in the death zone, you
know? That's why we're the dark side.
>> Julian, when did you know today like,
oh, we got them? Like when was that
moment? honestly
mid first quarter. Um and it's it's not
necessarily like okay like yeah like
we're gonna jump ahead or anything like
that. It's like okay they have to earn
each play. They might complete a pass
here or there. They might break a tackle
here or there but we're that's the
nature of our defense. We swarm to the
ball u and we make them line it up and
earn it each play. Um and it was just a
style. It was a style thing. Um they you
know they were getting excited. They got
you know a four or five yard run. Um and
then you know we create a negative play
the next play. Uh it's just us lining up
again and again on defense uh to just
impose our will.
>> Jul said that he thinks Withers is a
walking obviously in his career but what
does that say about the game that he had
>> Spoon man from the jump uh you know if
if the Dline's the soul of our defense
uh Spoon is a heart of it. I think you
know you can't cut on tape. Nah, you
can't watch tape if you know football or
or love football and you watch our tape.
21 jumps off the screen every single
day, every single game, every single
rep. Uh it's just raw talent. Uh it's
playing football the right way. He's
just a ball player and he's been that
way since the first time he stepped in
the building. And so yeah, three poor
Bulls a few all pros later. Um yeah, if
he keeps on this trajectory, uh he will
be all time great.
talk about your guys as
>> Yeah, man. This is just a complete team.
Um, we've won every game this year just
in different ways. Offense, balling, uh,
special teams coming through in the
clutch, defense doing our thing. Um, and
just we're just close. Like, we really
love each other and we love showing up
every day and going to work. It didn't
feel like work a single day this year.
And it's like what you it's what you
chase. It's what you dream. Um, and
usually it's just words. Usually you
just talk about how you want to act, but
it's how we lived. Um, we just love
spending time with each other and it
showed the way we're connected this
year.
>> Yeah.
Yeah.
>> I'm excited. Uh obviously, um I just,
you know, I love where I've come from.
Um it took a village for me to get here.
A lot of hard lessons, a lot of adverse
moments. Um and I'm happy because they
had a TV on in the locker room. I could
catch a glimpse of uh Bad Bunny's
performance. It was on mute. I didn't
hear anything, but uh it was cool just
to see uh on a special night.
>> Yeah.
It's I don't know. Uh it it's almost
like I don't want this to end. Um like
we love each other. Um I I go to work
happy, I leave happy. Um and even like
the challenging moments, like they're
all worth it because you're doing it
with people you love. Um and so it's
hard to process. Uh I don't know. It's
you just don't want this to end.
on the field.
>> It was different for sure pregame and,
you know, halftime and all the uh the
the TV timeouts, the little bonus times
in the middle, but when you step on
those white lines, we just play ball.
Like I just I think of it as 53 and 120
yard field. Um I just try to tell guys
this whole week like you're you're not
playing the moment. You're playing the
Patriots. Like you don't got to battle
all this. You're battling the people
across from you. And we've done that all
year. And when we when we think of it
like that, we play our best. No team can
compete.
>> Who?
>> Spoon. Uh I just, you know, talked about
it. He is special. Uh I think we all
look to him and how his style of play
is. He shows up and if you love
football, I mentioned if you watch
football, if you feel like you're a
football fan and you cut on our tape, 21
jumps off the screen. Uh maybe the stats
don't show it. maybe, you know, whatever
the analytics don't say whatever, but if
you watch him play, he's special and
it's every single play. Uh he gives his
all. Um and we feed off that. I look to
him as, you know, a leader of purpose uh
for this defense and yeah, he's going to
be all time great, I think.
>> Uh I was happy, man. I I asked uh who
got that one uh off and uh to be spoon I
think is really fitting. I think he was
been un for as talented as he is, all
the accolades he has, I still think he's
unsung. Um him and a few guys on our
defense that need to be talked about
more in a in a special way. Um because
Spoon's on a great trajectory.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> Of course. What does it say about?
>> Yeah, this is uh you know the
gratification is immediate in this
league. Um you want somebody to be a
star uh from day one and we had a lot of
guys who the story's been a little
different. Um you know Sam's one, I
think of Leonard Williams. Maybe Leo
might have been a star from the jump. Um
I think of myself. Uh I don't know. I
think
good pe good good people b find a way to
battle through it's it could have been
so easy 99% of people would have just
like ah I gave it into the pressure um
but Sam Darnold our our our leader our
captain he didn't you know he showed up
each day for the past eight years and
continue to get better continue to be
who he is uh and so for him to step up
take the field for us it's special we
love him so much because we know what
he's been through I know what he's been
through um and yeah I think Uh this
result speaks for itself.
>> Yeah.
>> Uh you know, he is a younger
quarterback. Obviously, he was an MVP,
you know, consideration this year. He
had a special season. Um we just felt we
had to rush one. Uh I think a lot of his
big-time plays made out were made
outside of the pockets, uh improvising
situations because he's incredibly
talented athlete in general. Um, and so
we felt good. We just knew we had to
follow our process. And it's not a
specific thing to them every single game
this year. If we know that we're at our
best, we're going to win the game. Um,
and I've been on teams that it hasn't
been that way. You can play perfect, you
still might lose. Um, and so for us, we
had the talent, we had the scheme, and
it's just connected and doing it
dayto-day.
>> Yeah, thank you. A lot of negative
plays. Uh we won the turnover battle
three to zero. Um yeah, I think we've
been special from the jump. It's it's
been cool to see an appreciation for our
guys uh you know each playoff game and
uh each uh ongoing moment.
>> I know. I know. We got to get our wind
right. We got to hit the hill or
condition a little more when we get back
here uh next few days because Yeah. I
wish we would have sealed the deal and
just pitched a shut out today. Uh but it
was it was a great effort.
>> Thank you.
>> How am I going to celebrate? Good amount
of tequila. Um a few cigars. Uh yeah,
we're going to have some fun.
>> Yeah.
>> The belief comes from him not taking any
shortcuts. We see him each day. He's
there early. He's there late. um he he's
committed to the process. Um he puts in
the work, but you know, there's so much
extra work that he puts in and above all
that, he's just a good guy. And so it's
so easy to tell love him and cheer for
him and to enjoy him being our captain.
Um and so yeah, as big of him to say,
but he's just been himself. Uh and we
just value him.
>> What's next for me? I'm gonna go home
back to Chicago with my son. We have a
second on the way in March and we're
just going to enjoy just being together
with our family. Um, I'm really excited
for that.
>> Uh, I think it's definitely going to
change
Super Bowl and we pitched a pretty good
game on defense. Um, and I don't know.
Uh, uh, I don't know. Uh, I think it's a
mixture of talent and but the the sum is
greater than kind of the individual
parts for us. But the individual parts
are really special. I think people need
to take notice of that. If you look
across our whole defense, people are
playing some great ball all season. And
so now we might get a little more
attention, but from the jump, the
process has never been different or
never been uh it hasn't changed up for
us at all. We we're consistent each day.
>> Thank you all very much.
>> Last one.
>> Say it again.
Thank you for support and love. Uh,
Alito, I love you. Thank you.